{"data":[{"question":"You didn't let me help you. If we _________ in turn, you _________ so tired.","a":"drove, wouldn't","b":"drove, didn't get","c":"had driven, wouldn't have got","d":"were driving, wouldn't get","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Conditional Sentence Type 3: used to talk about things that didn't happened in the past and the consequence if they had happened \n+ Form: if + Past Perfect, would + have + Past Participle","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"69","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"If there were no subjunctive mood , English ___ much easier.","a":"would have been","b":"will be","c":"would be","d":"could have been","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Conditional Sentence Type 2: used to talk about unlikely, imaginary or untrue events or situations \n- Form: if + Simple Past, would + Infinitive","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"69","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"If James had studied harder, he ___.","a":"had passed the exam","b":"would pass the exam","c":"would have passed the exam","d":"should pass the exam","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Conditional Sentence Type 3: used to talk about things that didn't happened in the past and the consequence if they had happened \n+ Form: if + Past Perfect, would + have + Past Participle","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"69","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"If my lawyer ___ here in the police station the day before yesterday, he ___ me from being detained.","a":"had been, would prevent","b":"had been, would have prevented","c":"were, would have prevented","d":"were, would prevent","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Conditional Sentence Type 3: used to talk about things that didn't happened in the past and the consequence if they had happened \n+ Form: if + Past Perfect, would + have + Past Participle","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"69","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"If Yvonne ___, she ___ that poisoned soup. \"Luckily she was sent to the hospital immediately.\"","a":"had been warned, would not have eaten","b":"was warned, would not eat","c":"would have been warned, had not eaten","d":"would be warned, had not eaten","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Conditional Sentence Type 3: used to talk about things that didn't happened in the past and the consequence if they had happened \n+ Form: if + Past Perfect, would + have + Past Participle","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"69","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"I didn't see your brother at the meeting. If he ___, he would have met my sister.","a":"did come","b":"has come","c":"had come","d":"came","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Conditional Sentence Type 3: used to talk about things that didn't happened in the past and the consequence if they had happened \n+ Form: if + Past Perfect, would + have + Past Participle","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"69","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"Without electricity, our life _________ quite different nowadays.","a":"will be","b":"is","c":"would be","d":"would have been","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Conditional Sentence Type 2: used to talk about unlikely, imaginary or untrue events or situations \n- Form: if + Simple Past, would + Infinitive","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"69","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"Tracy told Dan how to get here, but perhaps she ___ for him.","a":"must have written it out","b":"had to write it out","c":"ought to write it out","d":"should have written it out","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Should have PP: used to say what would have been right or sensible, but was not done","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"69","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"I stayed at a hotel while in Berlin. \"Oh, did you? You _________ with Robert.\"","a":"could stay","b":"could have stayed","c":"must have stayed","d":"would stay","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Could have PP: used to say that something was a possibility in the past, but did not actually happen","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"69","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"I was really worried about you. You _________ home without a word.","a":"needn't leave","b":"mustn't leave","c":"shouldn't have left","d":"couldn't have left","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Should have PP: used for saying what was the right thing to do when you realize that someone did not do it","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"69","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"}]}